finviz.com 2018-11-05

# Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY FOR INFORMATION USE AT FINVIZ.COM

Last updated on Jan 01, 2009

FINVIZ.com, ("We") are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using the FINVIZ.com web site. This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit www.finviz.com. 

## Personal Information We Collect

Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number or similar information. We only collect personal information on our web site that you choose to share with us, such as when:   

  * contacting us via the web site or email 
  * creating an user account 
  * creating personal content (presets, portfolios, private discussion) 
  * making an online purchase, or subscription to a service 

## How We Use Information Collected

We may use information in the following ways:

  * For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information.  

  * To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you.  

  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services.  

  * To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns 

Except as specifically stated in this privacy policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information with any third parties outside of FINVIZ.com 

## Security

The personally information is stored in our limited-access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. Online purchases made through our web site are processed securely by PayPal.com. When making a payment, we do not have access to your personal and credit card information. 

## Links

We may make content or services from other web sites including our co-branded web sites available to you from links located on www.finviz.com. These other web sites are not subject to this privacy policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each such web site to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

## Cookies

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a browser can record after visiting a web site. We may use cookies for technical purposes such as to enable better navigation through our site, or to store user preferences for interacting with the site. If you do not wish to have cookies stored on your machine, you can turn them off in your browser, it will not affect the overall functioning of the web site. 

## Internet-based Transfers

Given that the internet is a global environment, using the internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing www.finviz.com and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way. 

## Custom Privacy Settings

We allow registered users to select their preferred level of privacy. The additional privacy settings can be found in My Account > My Profile > Privacy Settings. 

## Comments and Questions

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy policy, you may contact us.
